{"test_questions": [[{"question": "The SQL command to create a table is:", "opta": "MAKE TABLE.", "optb": "ALTER TABLE.", "optc": "DEFINE TABLE.", "optd": "CREATE TABLE.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A ________ is a stored program that is attached to a table or a view.", "opta": "pseudofile", "optb": "embedded SELECT statement", "optc": "trigger", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The DROP TABLE statement:", "opta": "deletes the table structure only.", "optb": "deletes the table structure along with the table data.", "optc": "works whether or not referential integrity constraints would be violated.", "optd": "is not an SQL statement.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SQL views can be used to hide:", "opta": "columns and rows only.", "optb": "complicated SQL syntax only.", "optc": "both of the above can be hidden by an SQL view.", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The SQL statement to create a view is:", "opta": "CREATE VIEW.", "optb": "MAKE VIEW.", "optc": "SELECT VIEW.", "optd": "INSERT VIEW.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To update an SQL view, the DBMS must be able to associate the column(s) to be updated with:", "opta": "a particular column in a particular underlying table.", "optb": "a particular column in a particular row.", "optc": "a particular row in a particular underlying table.", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of SQL constraint?", "opta": "PRIMARY KEY", "optb": "FOREIGN KEY", "optc": "ALTERNATE KEY", "optd": "UNIQUE", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A ________ is a program that performs some common action on database data and that is stored in the database.", "opta": "trigger", "optb": "stored procedure", "optc": "pseudofile", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "For what purposes are views used?", "opta": "To hide columns only", "optb": "To hide rows only", "optc": "To hide complicated SQL statements only", "optd": "All of the above are uses for SQL views.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is an SQL virtual table that is constructed from other tables?", "opta": "Just another table", "optb": "A view", "optc": "A relation", "optd": "Query results", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When using the SQL INSERT statement:", "opta": "rows can be modified according to criteria only.", "optb": "rows cannot be copied in mass from one table to another only.", "optc": "rows can be inserted into a table only one at a time only.", "optd": "rows can either be inserted into a table one at a time or in groups.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is not an advantage of stored procedures?", "opta": "Greater security", "optb": "SQL can be optimized", "optc": "Code sharing", "optd": "Increased network traffic", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A reason for using an SQL view to hide columns is:", "opta": "to simplify a result only.", "optb": "to prevent the display of sensitive data only.", "optc": "to accomplish both of the above.", "optd": "None of the above are reasons for using an SQL view.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is an SQL trigger supported by Oracle?", "opta": "BEFORE", "optb": "INSTEAD OF", "optc": "AFTER", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The SQL ALTER statement can be used to:", "opta": "change the table structure.", "optb": "change the table data.", "optc": "add rows to the table.", "optd": "delete rows from the table.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What SQL structure is used to limit column values of a table?", "opta": "The LIMIT constraint", "optb": "The CHECK constraint", "optc": "The VALUE constraint", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which is NOT one of the most common types of SQL CHECK constraints?", "opta": "System date", "optb": "Range checks", "optc": "Lists of values", "optd": "Comparing one column value to another within the same table", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is an advantage of placing computations in SQL views?", "opta": "To save users from having to write an expression.", "optb": "To ensure that the results are consistent.", "optc": "To accomplish both of the above.", "optd": "None of the above is correct - computations cannot be placed in a view.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Views constructed from SQL SELECT statements that conform to the SQL-92 standard may not contain:", "opta": "GROUP BY.", "optb": "WHERE.", "optc": "ORDER BY.", "optd": "FROM.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}